Guide to Tuli Kupferberg and Sylvia Topp Papers MSS.385
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VI. Research and Source Material, 1821-2010; 1960-1995; 70 Linear Feet in 50 record cartons, 23 manuscript boxes, 1 flat folder, 2 flat boxes, 5 oversize flat boxes
  - Subseries A. Research and Subject files, 1821-2010; 1960-1995; 52 Linear Feet in 50 record cartons, 1 flat box, 1 flat folder, 2 oversize flat boxes
    - Fuck the Boss, undated (Box 69, Folder 28)
    - Fuck U Fuck Me, 1999 (Box 69, Folder 29)
    - Fucks, 1991 (Box 69, Folder 30)
    - Fucks at Home, 1993 (Box 69, Folder 31)
    - Funerals, Obituaries, Dying, 1979-1980 (Box 69, Folder 32)
    - Gay, 1964-1968 (Box 69, Folder 33)
    - Gay Erotica / Porn, Gay Rights, Student Homophile League, 1968, undated (Box 69, Folder 34)
    - Gay Rights, Mattachine, Vietnam, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 35)
    - General Humor, 1962, 1973-1980 (Box 69, Folder 36)
    - George M. Cohan, 2004 (Box 69, Folder 37)
    - George Washington, undated (Box 69, Folder 38)
    - German and French Language Protests, 1968-1969 (Box 69, Folder 39)
    - German Posters, circa 1974-1976 (Box 69, Folder 40)
    - Germany, undated (Box 69, Folder 41)
    - Getty-Trust Mom in Science, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 42)
    - Gingrich and Clinton, 1991-1995 (Box 69, Folder 43)
    - Ginzags [Ginsberg], 1997-2003 (Box 69, Folder 44)
    - Ginsberg, 1996-1997 (Box 69, Folder 45)
    - Giuliani via Lederman, 2000 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Glean 1, 1966, undated (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Glean 2, 1925, undated (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Global Marketing, undated (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Globe, 1986-1990 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - God's Moral Values, 1987-1992 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Going Postal, 1996 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Gonorrhea, 1966 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Good Cartoons By Others, 1981-1994 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Good Illustrations, 1971-1980 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Goodbye Cruel World, undated (Box 70, Folder 11-12)
    - Gossip, 1978-1982 (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - Government, 1963-1964 (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - Governments, 1969, undated (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - Grad School Days, 2008 (Box 70, Folder 16)
    - Graphic Design / Possible Fonts, 1958, undated (Box 70, Folder 17)
    - Graphic Design -- Thackeray, 1983-1990 (Box 70, Folder 18)
    - The Graves of Academe, undated (Box 70, Folder 19)
    - Great Books Photocopies, undated (Box 70, Folder 20)
    - The Great Depression, 1969, undated (Box 70, Folder 21)
    - "Great Moments in Journalism", 1974, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 22)
    - "Great Moments in Medicine", 1965-1966 (Box 70, Folder 23)
    - Green Left Weekly, 2002 (Box 70, Folder 24)
    - Greenwich Village, 1958-1979 (Box 70, Folder 25-26)
    - Greenwich Village Articles and References, 1958-1966 (Box 70, Folder 27)
    - Greenwich Village Folk Protests -- The Right to Sing Committee, 1961 (Box 70, Folder 28)
    - Guardian Weekend -- Karl Marx -- Francis Wheen, 1999 (Box 70, Folder 29)
    - Guatemala, 1989-1999 (Box 70, Folder 30)
    - Guiltless, 1923-1982 (Box 70, Folder 31)
    - Gulf War -- Dolly Parton, 1991-1995 (Box 70, Folder 32)
    - Gun Control, 1905-1989 (Box 70, Folder 33-35, Box 71, Folder 1-4)
    - Guy's Hospital Gazette, 1958 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - "Hail to the Chief Murderer", 2000 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Hair, 1969-1970 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Harvard, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Harvard (University), 1991-2000 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - "Hate and Fear", 1974 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Health, 1980-2008 (Box 71, Folder 11-14)
    - Health and Medicine, 1987-1993 (Box 71, Folder 15-16)
    - Health and Money, undated (Box 71, Folder 17)
    - Health and Nutrition Articles, 1986-2001 (Box 71, Folder 18)
    - Health and Strength, 1967, 1986-1989 (Box 71, Folder 19)
    - Health and Wealth, 2000 (Box 71, Folder 20)
    - Health, Drugs, Medicine, 1948-1968 (Box 71, Folder 21)
    - Health Insurance, 1992-1993 (Box 71, Folder 22)
    - Health Magazines, 2001-2002 (Box 71, Folder 23)
    - Hearst, undated (Box 71, Folder 24)
    - Heiko Questions / Email Exchange, 2003 (Box 71, Folder 25)
    - Hempstead Sentinel, 1928 (Box 71, Folder 26)
    - Hernia and Medical, 1974-1979 (Box 71, Folder 27)
    - "Hey Monk! Teach Yourself Fucking", undated (Box 71, Folder 28)
    - H.G. Wells The Desert Daisy, undated (Box 71, Folder 29)
    - Hippies, 1969-1970 (Box 71, Folder 30)
    - Hippies and Radical Press, 1967-1969 (Box 71, Folder 31)
    - Hippies, Protests, Retail, 1967-1969 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Hitler and Stalin, 2000-2001 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - "Hooks You and Kills Us", 2000 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Horseguard -- Horseshit, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Hot New Illustrations, 1999-2000 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - How to Kill Safely, 1991 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - "How to Save the World", undated (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Humor, 1976-1980 (Box 72, Folder 8-9)
    - Humor and Joke Memos, undated (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Humor and Love, 1979-1989 (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Humor, Writing, Book Collecting, 1998-2005 (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Hunting and Animals, 1961-1965 (Box 72, Folder 13-14)
    - Ideas, 1981, 1995-2001 (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - "I'll Be Poem For X-mas", 1978, undated (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - Illustrations, 1890, 1914, 1960-1994 (Box 72, Folder 17-31)
    - Illustrations 5-1, 1968-2003 (Box 72, Folder 32)
    - Illustrations 5-2, 1992-2003 (Box 73, Folder 1-2)
    - Illustrations 5-3, 2001, 2003, undated (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Illustrations 5-4, 2002-2003 (Box 73, Folder 4-5)
    - Illustrations 5-5, 1999-2003 (Box 73, Folder 6-7)
    - Illustrations of Gulf War, 1991 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Illustrations of People, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Illustrations, Perverbs, Oulipo, MoMA Surrealism, 1962, 1976, undated (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Illustrations, Phrenology, undated (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Illustrations -- Possible, 1979-1981 (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - Illustrations -- Rejected, 1918, 1964-1981 (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - Illustrations -- Sex, 1960-1983, undated (Box 73, Folder 14-15)
    - Images, 1969-1994 (Box 73, Folder 16)
    - Images of Christ, 1959, undated (Box 73, Folder 17)
    - "Imelda Possessions", 1989-1990 (Box 73, Folder 18)
    - Imperialism and Government, 1978, undated (Box 73, Folder 19)
    - Individuals, 1978 (Box 73, Folder 20)
    - Industry and Revolution Illustrations, 1969, undated (Box 73, Folder 21)
    - Internet, 1997-1999 (Box 73, Folder 22)
    - Intro Material, 1969-1970 (Box 73, Folder 23)
    - Investment, undated (Box 73, Folder 24)
    - Investment Fraud, 2000 (Box 73, Folder 25)
    - Iraq, 1991 (Box 73, Folder 26)
    - Iraq War, 2002-2005 (Box 73, Folder 27)
    - Iraq War and Protests, 1992-2005 (Box 73, Folder 28)
    - Iraq War, Death Penalty, Imprisonment, 1985-2001 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Ireland, 1985-1991 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Is It Torture Yet? (David Underhill), 2005 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Israel, 1995-1998 (Box 74, Folder 4-5)
    - Israel and Miscellaneous Possibles, 2000-2001 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - It All Depends, 1988 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Jeff Lewis [Ginsberg], 1997, 2004, undated (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Jew Comics -- "Vos Makhit a Yid?", 2006 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Jew Nose / Juneaus, undated (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Jew Songs (Long Shot), 1995 (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Jews, 1954-2002 (Box 74, Folder 12-24)
    - Jews and Anti-Semitism, 1966-1984 (Box 74, Folder 25)
    - Jews and Arabs, 1984-1985 (Box 74, Folder 26)
    - Jews and Zionism, 1988 (Box 74, Folder 27)
    - Jews, Anti-Semitism, Father Coughlin, 1940-1979 (Box 74, Folder 28)
    - "The Jig is Up", circa 1985 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Joan's Kids, Rejects, 1959 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Joe's Pub Protest Song -- Vietnam Songbook, 2003 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Joey Adams, 1979-1980 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Joey Heller, 1999 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - John Brown, undated (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - John Kehoe Letter / Messenger Service Fiscal Statement, 1954-2008 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - John Reed at Morristown (NJ) High, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Jokes and Ads, 1971, undated (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Journalism, and Committee to Defend Journalists, 1961-1982, 1994-1996 (Box 75, Folder 10-12)
    - Journalism and Reporting, 1984-1987 (Box 75, Folder 13-14)
    - Judaism and Israel / Palestine, 1982-1985 (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - Jury Duty, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 16)
    - Kaleidoscope, Washington Free Press, 1968-1969 (Box 75, Folder 17-18)
    - Karl and the Kommunists, undated (Box 75, Folder 19)
    - Karl, Liebknecht, 1969 (Box 75, Folder 20)
    - Karl Marx, circa 1994 (Box 75, Folder 21)
    - Karl Marx: Biographical Memoirs -- Wilhelm Liebknecht, undated (Box 75, Folder 22)
    - Karl Marx Song Bibliography, 1995-2006 (Box 75, Folder 23)
    - Karl Pubcrawl, 1969-1984 (Box 75, Folder 24)
    - Karl and Wurmbrand, 2001 (Box 75, Folder 25)
    - Keep Your Eye Off the Prize, 1989-1990 (Box 75, Folder 26)
    - Kerrey, 1982-2001 (Box 75, Folder 27)
    - K.F.P.A. Mailing List, 1987-1991 (Box 75, Folder 28-29)
    - "Kiddie Porn" Illustrations -- High Times Article On Children at War, 1970-1990 (Box 75, Folder 30)
    - "Kill for Peace" -- Clippings, 1968-1969 (Box 75, Folder 31-32)
    - "Kill for Peace" -- New, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 33)
    - "Kill Them All", undated (Box 75, Folder 34)
    - Kissinger, 1999-2000, undated (Box 75, Folder 35)
    - Klub Weimar, 1992, undated (Box 75, Folder 36)
    - Kronenberger -- The Cutting Edge, undated (Box 75, Folder 37)
    - Kruschev's U.S. Visit, 1959-1960 (Box 75, Folder 38)
    - La Prima Internazionale in Halia, undated (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Labor and Hebrew Jews, circa 1989 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Labor History, 1995 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Labour Party Song Sheet, circa 1955 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Lach Un Sai Freilach / Laugh and Be Happy Sheet Music, 1950 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Ladies Kennel Club, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Langan Covers Internet, 1989-2000 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Law, 1963-2006 (Box 76, Folder 8-9)
    - Law Research -- Clippings, 1977-1997 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Law Research -- Courtly News, Capital Punishment of Animals, 1972-1982 (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Law Research -- La Salle -- Greenwich Village Police -- D.O.J., 1962-1978 (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Lawyer vs. Doctor, 1976-1979 (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - Leads for Cartoons / Collages, 1993-1996 (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - League of Sexual Freedom / Jeff Poland, 1964-1967 (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - Lee Scharf (and Originals), 1989 (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - Leftists Publication -- Letter from Joanne Aquino, 1970, undated (Box 76, Folder 17)
    - Lennon and Liberty, 2000 (Box 76, Folder 18)
    - Letter Type, undated (Box 76, Folder 19)
    - Lies of Government, undated (Box 76, Folder 20)
    - Life, 1978-1983 (Box 76, Folder 21)
    - Listen to the Mockingbird Lyrics, undated (Box 76, Folder 22)
    - Listen to the Mockingbird -- Research, 1989-1991 (Box 76, Folder 23)
    - Literary Feuds, 1988-1989 (Box 76, Folder 24)
    - "Loompanics Unlimited" Articles and Illustrations, 1981-1999 (Box 76, Folder 25)
    - Looting, 1967, undated (Box 76, Folder 26)
    - Love, 1962-1968, undated (Box 76, Folder 27-28)
    - Love Letters, undated (Box 76, Folder 29)
    - Ludd, 1984, undated (Box 76, Folder 30)
    - Lustlore Research, 1959-1983 (Box 76, Folder 31-32)
    - Machismo, undated (Box 76, Folder 33)
    - Macmullen -- Enemies of the Roman Order, 1966 (Box 76, Folder 34)
    - Macy's Christmas Advertisement, 1985-2001 (Box 76, Folder 35)
    - Madness and Insanity, 1965, undated (Box 76, Folder 36)
    - Mai Graffiti -- Franke 1968, circa 1968 (Box 76, Folder 37)
    - Marcus Aurelius, undated (Box 76, Folder 38-39)
    - Margie Rogerson and Bob Dylan -- Listen Robert Moses Song Lyrics, 1997-1998, undated (Box 76, Folder 40)
    - Marine Killers, undated (Box 76, Folder 41)
    - Marines, 2000 (Box 76, Folder 42)
    - Marital Aids, 1967-1968 (Box 76, Folder 43)
    - Marx and Marxism -- Ajit Jain, Alexander J. Matejko, 1984 (Box 76, Folder 44)
    - Marx, Bloomberg, 1978-2003 (Box 76, Folder 45)
    - Marx -- Correspondence, 1995, 1998 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Marx -- Genealogy and Chronology, 1992, 1995, undated (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Marx Graphics, 1970, undated (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Marx Images, 1971, undated (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Marx in London, 1970-1979, 1995, undated (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Marx -- Miscellaneous, 1972-1999 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Marx -- Notes and Fragments, undated (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Mastheads and Editorial Lists, 1983 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Max Kollskegg, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Mayakovsky Article -- Industrial Psychology, 1949, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Maybes, 2006 (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - McReynolds, 2000 (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - Meander, Mark Twain, Between Books and Life, 2006-2007 (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - Meat, 1961-1967, undated (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - Media Reform -- Common Dreams, 1995-2004 (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - Medical, 1958-1977 (Box 77, Folder 16)
    - Medical and Health, 1978-1981 (Box 77, Folder 17)
    - Medical and Health Info, 1980-1981 (Box 77, Folder 18)
    - Medical Articles, 1962-1964, 1998-2002 (Box 77, Folder 19-20)
    - Medical Illustration, 1962-1981 (Box 77, Folder 21)
    - Medical Illustrations, 1953-1965, undated (Box 77, Folder 22-24)
    - Medical -- Miscellaneous, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 25)
    - Medical Poets, 1952-2000 (Box 77, Folder 26)
    - Medical Quotes, 1964-1978 (Box 77, Folder 27)
    - Medical Research, 1968, 1983 (Box 77, Folder 28-29)
    - Medicine, 1961-1998 (Box 77, Folder 30-31)
    - Medicine and Disease, 1990-1993 (Box 77, Folder 32)
    - Medicine and Health, 1963-1978 (Box 77, Folder 33)
    - Medicine and Surgery, 1962-1978 (Box 77, Folder 34)
    - Memorial Notices, 1977-1979 (Box 77, Folder 35)
    - Memos, Correspondence, Notes, Drafts, 2006-2008, undated (Box 78, Folder 1-2)
    - Mendele, 1995 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Mendez -- Flohr -- The Jew in the Modern World, 1952-1980 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Merry -- Mount, undated (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Michael Korda, Man to Man, 1996 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Microeconomics, 1958-2001 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - The Middle Finger, 1992-1999 (Box 78, Folder 8-9)
    - Militarism, 1963-1973 (Box 78, Folder 10-11)
    - Military, 1969-1970 (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Military, Atlas Chemicals, 1965-1969 (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - Military / Drugs, 1970 (Box 78, Folder 14)
    - Military Families, 2001 (Box 78, Folder 15)
    - Military, Shootings, Workplace, 1928, 1978-2007 (Box 78, Folder 16)
    - Military, War, Hard-Hat Riot, 1969-1999 (Box 78, Folder 17)
    - Miranda [Rights] -- Revised, 1995 (Box 78, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous, 1833, 1877, 1950-2007, undated (Box 78, Folder 19-30, Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous, 1980s, 1983-1986 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Clippings -- People, 1975-2002 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Cuts, 1909, 1948, 1959-1960 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Illustrations, 1969-1971, 1999, undated (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Items, Clippings, and Songs, 1952-1953, 1977-1987, 2006-2007 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Leads for Collages / Cartoons, 1996 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Poetry Material, 2004-2008 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Mixed Articles, 2001-2003 (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Mixed Correspondence, 2001-2003 (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - Mixed -- Drugs, Police, Miscellaneous, 1969-1971 (Box 79, Folder 11-12)
    - Mixed Loose Material, 1991-2001 (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - Montagnard, 1971 (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - Moon Landing, 1969 (Box 79, Folder 15)
    - Mordecai Vanunu, 1991-1997 (Box 79, Folder 16)
    - Moses and Management, 1965 (Box 79, Folder 17)
    - Most Expensive -- Collecting / Luxury Items, 1972-1975 (Box 79, Folder 18-19)
    - Mother Fuckers, 2000 (Box 79, Folder 20)
    - Mountaineering, 1969-1974 (Box 79, Folder 21)
    - Mozart Articles, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 22)
    - Murder Kid, 1998 (Box 79, Folder 23)
    - Murder of Gary Carotenuti, 1969 (Box 79, Folder 24)
    - "Murdered to the Music of Bob Dylan", 1989 (Box 79, Folder 25)
    - Music, 1980-2001 (Box 79, Folder 26-29)
    - Music and Art -- Possibles, 1989-1995 (Box 79, Folder 30)
    - Music and Madness, 1968-1998 (Box 79, Folder 31-32)
    - Music and Poetry, 1989-1990 (Box 79, Folder 33)
    - Music Illustrations, 1999 (Box 79, Folder 34)
    - Music Miscellany, 2002-2005 (Box 79, Folder 35)
    - "Music Our Forefathers Sang", circa 1975 (Box 79, Folder 36)
    - My Pious Friends, 1928 (Box 79, Folder 37)
    - "Myself When Young", 2003 (Box 79, Folder 38)
    - Nation of Islam, Civil Rights, 1962-1963 (Box 79, Folder 39)
    - National Campaign Magazine, 1972 (Box 79, Folder 40)
    - National Target Company, undated (Box 79, Folder 41)
    - Nazis and Miscellaneous, 1995-2001 (Box 79, Folder 42-43)
    - New Age, 1987 (Box 79, Folder 44)
    - "The New America", undated (Box 79, Folder 45)
    - New England, 1990-1992 (Box 79, Folder 46)
    - New Jew Circumcision, 1993-1994 (Box 79, Folder 47)
    - The New Jewish Baby Book -- Anita Diamant, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 48)
    - New Music Seminar, 1990 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - New Stuff, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - New York, 1953-1958 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - New York City Photographs -- Old, 1980-1988 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - News Articles / Memos, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - News Items and Clippings, 1971-1974 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Newsheads, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Newsphotos, 1969-1971 (Box 80, Folder 8-9)
    - Newspoems / Poems -- Photocopies and Clippings, 1972, undated (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Nike and The Beatles, circa 1987 (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Nixon Inauguration, 1968-1969 (Box 80, Folder 12-13)
    - No Circ [Circumcision], 1980-1998 (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - No Shredder, 2000-2001 (Box 80, Folder 15)
    - NOCIRC Newsletter, 1980-1994 (Box 80, Folder 16)
    - Northcliffe (Great Moments in History of Journalism), undated (Box 80, Folder 17)
    - Notecards, Memo Cards, and Clippings, 1959-1993 (Box 80, Folder 18)
    - Notes and Music Articles, 1996-2006 (Box 80, Folder 19)
    - Notes, Articles, Quotes, 2003-2008 (Box 80, Folder 20)
    - Notes / Fragments, undated (Box 80, Folder 21)
    - Nova Zembla, 1993 (Box 80, Folder 22)
    - Nuclear Fallout Shelters and Recovery -- Civil Defense Commission -- "Master Detective" Articles, 1958-1974 (Box 80, Folder 23-24)
    - Nuclear Rockets and Weapons, 1957-1962 (Box 80, Folder 25)
    - Nudity, 1995-1999 (Box 80, Folder 26)
    - Nun Better, 1965-1981 (Box 80, Folder 27)
    - Nutrition and Healthcare, 1968-1973 (Box 80, Folder 28-29)
    - NYC League for Sexual Freedom, Committee for Freedom of the Arts -- Flyers, Handbills, Announcements -- Dick Higgins, 1964 (Box 80, Folder 30)
    - NYC League for Sexual Freedom -- Flyers, Handbills -- LEMAR, 1960-1966 (Box 80, Folder 31)
    - NYPD -- Smoking Letter, undated (Box 80, Folder 32)
    - Obscenity Legislation, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 33)
    - Occult and Mystical, 1977, undated (Box 80, Folder 34)
    - OJ Simpson, 1995 (Box 80, Folder 35)
    - OK -- Japan -- KO, undated (Box 80, Folder 36)
    - Old Map of Brooklyn, undated (Box 80, Folder 37)
    - Old Time Illustrations, undated (Box 80, Folder 38)
    - Olday, undated (Box 80, Folder 39)
    - On Yiddish -- NY Times, 2008 (Box 80, Folder 40)
    - "Oops, Sorry!", 1962-1983 (Box 80, Folder 41)
    - Open Letter, 1953-1968 (Box 80, Folder 42)
    - Oppose Book Worship [Mao Tse-Tung], 1966 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - "Or We'll Start Fasting", 1992 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Organized Vengeance Called Justice -- Peter Kropotkin, 2009 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Osama Bin Laden Articles, 1998 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Other Mags, 1981-1983 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Other People's Poetry, undated (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Other Speaking Pictures, 1975 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Our Century, 1918, 1957-1983, undated (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - "Over 47", 1935-1969 (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - "Over 52", 1968-1969 (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - "Over 54", 1968-1969 (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - Oxford Applications, 1992-1995 (Box 81, Folder 12)
    - Paradise in Bethlehem, 1997 (Box 81, Folder 13)
    - Parody Songs, 1978, undated (Box 81, Folder 14)
    - Parting With Illusions -- Vladimir Pozner, undated (Box 81, Folder 15)
    - Past and Present Illustrations -- NYC, 1964-1966 (Box 81, Folder 16)
    - Peace Quotes (Robert Wolfe), 1961, undated (Box 81, Folder 17)
    - Peacemaker / Anti-Gun Material, 1981-1983 (Box 81, Folder 18)
    - Pedlars, undated (Box 81, Folder 19)
    - Penis, undated (Box 81, Folder 20)
    - People Art, 1986 (Box 81, Folder 21)
    - People You Know -- George Ade, circa 1902 (Box 81, Folder 22)
    - Personal and Research, 1974-1975 (Box 81, Folder 23)
    - Personal Unsorted Files, 1996-1997 (Box 81, Folder 24)
    - Peru, 1990 (Box 81, Folder 25)
    - Phantasy Productions Listserv, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 26)
    - Philip Morris / Altria, 2003-2007 (Box 81, Folder 27)
    - Philip Morris: Raising Kids Who Don't Smoke Brochures, 2003 (Box 81, Folder 28)
    - Photographs and Illustrations, 1969-1971 (Box 81, Folder 29)
    - Photographs for Cartoons, 1978-1989 (Box 81, Folder 30-31)
    - Phuc Nam, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 32)
    - Physical Culture, 1928 (Box 81, Folder 33)
    - Piss Head, 2001 (Box 81, Folder 34)
    - Plastic Surgery, 1999-2000 (Box 81, Folder 35)
    - Playboy -- The Decent Society, 1968-1969 (Box 81, Folder 36)
    - Playgrounds, 1966-1981 (Box 81, Folder 37)
    - Poetry, 1948, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 38)
    - Poetry by the Homeless, 1985 (Box 81, Folder 39)
    - Poetry Research, 1969-1980 (Box 81, Folder 40)
    - Poets, 1993 (Box 81, Folder 41)
    - Poland, 1991 (Box 81, Folder 42)
    - Police, 1957-2001 (Box 81, Folder 43-46, Box 82, Folder 1-6)
    - Police and Religion, 1961-1982 (Box 82, Folder 7-8)
    - Police Corruption, 1987-1988 (Box 82, Folder 9-10)
    - Police -- Work, 1968-1969 (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - Political Images, 1991-1994 (Box 82, Folder 12)
    - Political / Protest Flyers and Clippings, 1960s (Box 82, Folder 13-22, Box 83, Folder 1-3)
    - Politics, 1976 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Politics and Government, 1977-1978 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Politics and Personality, 1965 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Politics / Politicians, 1960-1976 (Box 83, Folder 7-8)
    - Politricks, 1976-1978 (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Pols Fight, 1992 (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - Poorhouse, 1996 (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - Popular Poetry, 1962-1964 (Box 83, Folder 12)
    - Pornography and Feminism, 1970-1974 (Box 83, Folder 13)
    - Pornography and Sex, 1973-1980 (Box 83, Folder 14)
    - Pornography / Bicentennial, 1976 (Box 83, Folder 15)
    - Possible for Cartoons, 1993-1997 (Box 83, Folder 16)
    - Possible [Mixed Clippings], 1995-1997 (Box 83, Folder 17)
    - Possibles, 1915, 1968-2007 (Box 83, Folder 18-28)
    - Possibles -- British Ad Typography Book, 1952, 1995 (Box 83, Folder 29)
    - Possibly, 1995 (Box 83, Folder 30)
    - Potato Chip Advert, 1995 (Box 83, Folder 31)
    - Poverty, 1981-1983, 2000 (Box 83, Folder 32)
    - Poverty and Healthcare, 1969-1978 (Box 83, Folder 33)
    - Power, 1963-1969 (Box 84, Folder 1-3)
    - The Power Network, undated (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Pres. Losers, 1997-1999 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Presidential Campaign Material, undated (Box 84, Folder 6-7)
    - Presidents, 2003, undated (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Primate [Animal Rights], 1987-1990 (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Primates Research, 1982-1994 (Box 84, Folder 10-11)
    - Primatology and Animals, 1985-1990 (Box 84, Folder 12-13)
    - Princess Diana, 1981-1997 (Box 84, Folder 14)
    - Princess Di, Elvis, Music, 1977-1998 (Box 84, Folder 15)
    - Prohibition Publications -- Drugs -- Tobacco, 1963-1973 (Box 84, Folder 16)